UX Related Skills

<u>Portfolio</u> My portfolio showcases interaction design and UX research: http://inhll.info

<u>Communication</u> I am a clear, concise writer and have experience collaborating with

interdisciplinary teams, both local and remote.

<u>CSS/HTML & Code</u> I am fluent in HTML, CSS and comfortable prototyping in Bootstrap. I have

completed Codecademy and Free Code Camp HTML/CSS/JS courses.

Applications I am fluent in Adobe Creative Suite, Microsoft Office, Google Docs,

Basecamp, Axure RP, Trello, Morae, Silverback, and many more.

Sketching & Drawing I sketch my ideas on paper to help solve problems creatively and clearly

explain my ideas. I have formal training in graphic facilitation methods.

Work Experience

User Experience Designer at ZS Associates, *Evanston*

August 2015 - Present

My work at ZS Associates focuses on improving the usability of enterprise pharmaceutical sales and compensation software. To kick off my work at ZS, I led a major research project focused on improving the efficacy of users when configuring one of our core tools. For this project I planned, designed, and performed primary research and analysis with international users, presented findings to internal stakeholders, and wireframed and validated the resulting designs. To bring this work to fruition, I worked with an international agile development team - attending backlog grooming, retros, demos - and helped create best practices to ensure effective UX support for development efforts.

Sr. Associate Interaction Designer at Manifest Digital, *Chicago*

August 2014 - August 2015

I solved meaningful problems by applying interaction design and user experience principles. My focus was on crafting award-winning enterprise insurance mobile experiences which helped customers accomplish their goals quickly and efficiently. I achieved this by developing process flows to understand the ecosystem, wireframe iterations, and by working closely with Quality Control and development teams.

Sr. Instructional Technology Consultant at DePaul University, *Chicago* January 2013 - July 2014 I provided course development and support on instructional tools for the nationally ranked College of Computing and Digital Media (CDM). My primary focus was planning for and facilitating the transition of 200+ CDM faculty from a home-grown learning management system to Desire2Learn. In addition to providing primary support for CDM, I assisted others on my team in supporting their faculty with my comprehensive system knowledge and administrator role in D2L.

<u>Instructional Technology Consultant</u> at DePaul University, *Chicago* 2013

September 2011 - January

In this role, I provided course development support to Senior Instructional Technology Consultants and departments in the College of Liberal Arts and Social Sciences. I also offered technical training and support for faculty by developing, maintaining, and delivering trainings and related materials. I led and supported the migration of documentation to a wiki, documented internal processes, responded to and submitted vendor tickets, and held a Supervisory Administrator role in D2L.

Enterprise Systems Administrator at DePaul University, *Chicago* July 2007 - September 2011

I provided internal and customer-facing application support in an environment of 24,000+ users, performed daily application administration (including patching, Building Block installation, and daily system maintenance) of Blackboard versions 6, 7, and 8. I also assisted with Wimba, TurnItln, Mailman, and Streaming Media systems administration. I led the migration of existing DePaul course materials from Blackboard to Desire2Learn.

Web Designer; Training & Support Rep. at SpringCM, Chicago 2007

September 2006 - June

In my role I was responsible for the creation of marketing materials for the company website, trade show booths, and web development responsibilities such as writing PHP / HTML / CSS, creating visual assets, and deployment of code to production. I was also responsible for developing training, print materials, email newsletters and other collateral related to marketing, and maintained the LINUX web development environment.

Education

MS in Human-Computer Interaction
DePaul University, Chicago
June 2016

Studying HCI/UX taught me the importance of air-tight research when observing complex interactions to determine the best way to meet the goals of product users and stakeholders.

BA in Geography, GIS concentration DePaul University, Chicago June 2004 Studying globalization and urbanization taught me the importance of observing complex systems and effectively communicating the big picture to incentivize action.

Professional Development

Completed The Grove's *Principles of Graphic Facilitation* workshop and all supplementary materials (2016). Attended *UX Immersions* (2016). Participated in *World Information Architecture Day Chicago* events on behalf of Manifest Digital (2015). Attended various UX Meetups and IXDA Events in Chicago (ongoing).